Jai Hind Welcome to the new informative video
Friends, if you have an
account in ICC Bank then this video is very important for you
because a
lot of changes have happened in ICC Bank
since August, like regarding cash withdrawal from ATM card,
everyone uses ATM card
and everyone does it daily,
but it is very important for you to know the
limit, a lot of changes have happened since this month,
so this is a very important
video for you, stay till the end of the video
and see what all the bank has done with it
and what is the limit of cash withdrawal from ATM as of today,
so let's start the video,
if you are new to our channel then
definitely go live and subscribe because we bring live
updates from the bank,
friends, I have taken you to the notice board of ICC Bank,
which is
in the notice board now, how are the recorded updates from ATM card, you will
see in this update, what is ICC Bank doing in the notice board,
they have changed a lot,
like you can see
what all changes have happened, from Young Star
Dividend Tax of Rs. 5000  The
limit that was there has been exhausted, you cannot do that.
You will no longer be able to withdraw money from Inno Debit Card, Scenery Citizen Silver Debit Card, Silver Debit Card, Scenery Citizen Card at Smart Shop. Apart from this, the Gold Plus
Debit Card, which was sold by the bank as a higher value card earlier, saying
that you
can withdraw high value cash,
now there is no concept of high value cash withdrawal from it
today. So, please note
that now the concept of Digital India is going on,
so how recording is a big concern,
so the bank has changed its policy. It is
possible that if you are an ICON customer, then an
email must have been sent to you. If not, then
you must send these updates to your friend circle
who has an account in ICC.
If you want to open an account in ICC, then
you must know this thing. You should know this,
but you should have the knowledge.
Apart from this, Expression Debit Card was
sold a lot earlier. Card with photo in ICON, you can withdraw cash up to
₹7 lakh on the photo card.  There was a
limit which you will not be able to withdraw now.
After that, there was a limit on Coral Debit Card, Expression
Debit Card, This Bank
Infinity Card, Rubik Debit Card and
Safidon Debit Card,
which has now been withdrawn. Now
you can withdraw cash only with one cash withdrawal limit,
so I will tell you how much you can withdraw.
Now see the withdrawal limit from ATM card
for regular banking,
if you have a regular savings account, then in this, there is an
account with MAP requirement of Rs 30,000.
Now the bank is asking
you for a cash withdrawal of Rs 2 lakh, so you can withdraw Rs 2 lakh from this.
You can
also withdraw cash of Rs 2 lakh monthly within a month, either
you can withdraw Rs 20,000 by doing Rs 10,000 each or you can withdraw Rs 2
lakh in one go, so your withdrawal limit is
nothing, it is a monthly exemption that you
can withdraw monthly, you cannot withdraw more than Rs 2 lakh
if ​​you have a regular
savings account.  If you have a previous
savings account, then I am maintaining ₹50,000 in it along with
₹2 lakh.
Asset linked account with zero balance
is applicable in it, so you can also deposit up to ₹500,000,
which was a very high
limit earlier. Those who have a Titanium account
again, the petrol limit was daily and
monthly unlimited, but now there is nothing like that.
Now if you have any debit card in a month,
I told you that the
petrol feature of Priyam Debit Card Sir has been banned,
so you can deposit ₹5 lakh.
If you have a salary account, it is
very important for salary customers. If you have a
salary account, then you can deposit up to ₹5 lakh.
That also depends. Many
corporates have ₹2 lakh and many have ₹5 lakh as well.
So, your relative should
check once what is the limit in their corporate, is it ₹
2 lakh or ₹5 lakh. Apart from that, ₹
7.30 lakh has been kept for wealth and private bank customers, which is of high value.  You
can do it, apart from this, salary credit has been given to
him up to Rs 2 lakh, so
I have already told you that you should
check with the corporate that what is their company
limit, how is the limit of the
employee, then there is a lot of changing,
it is very important that what is your
limit, so friends, do share the video with your friends
and in your friend circle
because it is a very important video
and what kind of recording is this because
ATM is doing the delivery, so you should
prefer UPI, in many videos in our channel,
I have
told about the method for payment through UPI in ICC Bank, so do
like and subscribe to our channel,
thank you very much